A Guide to the John C. Bugher papers FA027
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Articles, Speeches, Manuscripts, 2
  - "Delayed Radiation Effects at Hiroshima and Nagasaki", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Demonstration of Yellow Fever Antibodies in Animal Sera by the Intercerebral Protection Test in Mice", 1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "The Distribution of Radiostrontium (SR89) in Adult Mosquitoes of Three Species...", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Distribution of Radiostrontium in Mosquitoes...", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Effects of Fission Materials on Air, Sail and Living Species", 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Effects of Radiation", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "The Efficiency of Vaccination in the Prevention of Yellow Fever in Colombia", 1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Electronics in the Atomic Energy Commission ( AEC) Biomedical Program", 1953 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Epidemiology of Jungle Fever in Eastern Colombia", 1944 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "External Dose from Short-Lived Isotopes in Fallout from Nuclear Explosions", 1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "The Fallout Problem in Civil Defense Planning", 1955 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "A Frequency of Bone Sarcoma in the United States", 1958 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Health Perspectives of Our Radioactive World", 1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "International Aspects of Public Health", 1957 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Jungle Yellow Fever", 1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Lethality in Cell Populations From Intracellular Nuclear Reactions", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - "Medical Education Activities of The Rockefeller Foundation", 1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - "The Medical Effects of Atomic Blast", 1954 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - "Medical Uses of Atomic Energy", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - "Monkeys in Relation to Yellow Fever in Bwamba County, Uganda" (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - "Naturally Acquired Yellow Fever Immunity in Muzu, Colombia", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - "New Developments in Atomic Medicine", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - "New Horizons in Nuclear Energy", 1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "New Scientific Developments in the Area of Health", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - "The Next Five Years", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - "Notes on Program Plans for Medical Education and Public Health (MEPH)", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - "Nuclear Tests and the Public Welfare", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - "Observations During an Outbreak of Infectious Hepatitis in British West Africa", 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - "Organized Clinical Investigations of Cancer", 1937 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - "The Partnership of Research and Medical Practice", 1954 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - "Pathology as Applied to Police Science", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - "Precise Determination of Body Surface Area by Mechanical Quadrature", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - "The Preparation and Structure of Graded Collodion Membranes...", 1952 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - "The Probability of Chance Occurrence of Multiple Malignant Neoplasms", 1934 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - "Progress in Nuclear Energy - Series VI", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - "Progress in Nuclear Energy - Series VII", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - "The Puerto Rico Nuclear Research Reactor", 1961 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - "A Quinhydrome - Collodion Electrode of Special Applicability in Experimental Pathology", 1931 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - "Radiophosphous and Radiostrontium in Mosquitoes", 1949 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - "Radiation and Human Health", 1957 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - "Report on the Possibilities for Research in Virus Diseases in Japan", 1951 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - "Responses of Mosquitoes to Change in Microclimate", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Reviews, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - "The Role of the Pathologist in Modern Medicine", 1957 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - St. Louis University, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - "Scientific Objectivity and the Public Health", 1959 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - "Some Considerations of the Presence of Strontium 90 in the Environment of Man", 1956 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - "Some Problems of Interpretation of the Statistics of Cancer Diagnosis and Treatment", 1956 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - "The Stability of Chick Embryo Yellow Fever Vaccine during Storage", 1953 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - "Statement before the Joint Committee on Atomic Energy", 1955 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - "The Susceptibility of African Wild Animals to Yellow Fever", n.d. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - "Tentative Ideas Concerning the Development of Rockefeller Foundation Program in Medical Educaiton and Public Health (MEPH)", 1956 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - "Tomorrow's Atom and You", 1955 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - "Transition of the Atomic Energy Industry from Government to Private Control", 1955 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - "Triple Primary Carcinomas: With Two Case Reports", n.d. (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - "Ultracentrifugation Studies of a Urinary Mucoprotein which Reacts with Various Viruses", n.d. (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - "Ultrafiltration of Recently Isolated Neurotropic Viruses", 1952 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - "The Use of Radioactive Isotopes for Marking Mosquitoes", n.d. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - "Yellow Fever", 1956 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - "Yellow Fever", 1959 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- General Reprints, 3
  Alphabetical arrangement by subject.
  - A, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Research Council Radiobiological Laboratory, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Joseph and Stewart Alsop (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Cancer Society, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Nuclear Society, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Nuclear Society, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Energy in Canada, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Autoradiology Conference, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - B, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - B, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - William Berman, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - William Berman, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bharatival and Vaze "External Radiation Dose Received by the Inhabitants of Monazite..." (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Danko Bracic, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Leonard J. Bruce-Chwatt, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - C, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - C, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - C, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Ping Yao Cheng, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Civil Defense, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Council of State Governments, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - E. P. Cronkite, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - D, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - E, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - F, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - G, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - H, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Hearings, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - I, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Information Storage and Retrieval (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - J, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Joint Committee on Defense Production (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - K, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - L, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - M, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - N, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - N, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - National Committee on Radiation Protection, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - National Committee on Radiation Protection, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - National Committee on Radiation Protection, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - National Academy of Sciences - The Biological Effects of Atomic Radiation, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - National Committee on Radiation Protection, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - New York State General Advisory Committee, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - New York State General Advisory Committee, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - O, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Operation Troll, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - P, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - P, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - P, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Pathological Effects of Atomic Radiation, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Pathological Effects of Atomic Radiation, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Public Health Reports, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Public Health Reports, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Public Health Reports, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Public Health Engineering Abstracts, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Theodore Puck, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Puerto Rico Nuclear Center, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - R, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - R, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - R, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Radiation Sterilization of Foods, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Radioisotope Research Support Program, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - "The Role of Calcium on the Intestinal Absorption of Vitamin B12 in Tropical Sprue.", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - S, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - S, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - S, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - S, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Spanish Atomic Energy, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Stanford Research Institute, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Stanford Research Institute, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Statement on Radioactive Fallout, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Studies with Iragglutinable Erythrocyte Counts # -7, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - T, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Tests for Nuclear Flight Environment, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Thorium, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - John Tulles, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - United Kingdom Atomic Energy Authority, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - United Nations Radiation Committee, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - U, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 0086A)
  - V, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - W, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - W, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Shields Warren, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - World Health Organization (WHO), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - World Health Organization (WHO), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - World Health Organization (WHO) Expert Committee on Radiation, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - X-Z, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 94)
- Atomic Energy Commission, 4
  This series contains material on the Division of Biology and Medicine as well as research action summaries and tests.
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Distinguished Service Award, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Superior Accomplishment.
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Japan results; role of AEC lab; Federal Radiation Council; radioactive waste. James Horsfall.
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, 1958-March 1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, April 1960-July 1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, April 1960-July 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, April 1960-July 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, April 1960-July 1961 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Division of Biology and Medicine - Summary of Research Actions, April 1960-July 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Reactor Safety and Accidents, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Reactor Safety and Accidents - Reports (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Tests, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Tests, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - "Theoretical Possibilities and Consequences of Major Accidents in Large Nuclear Power Plants" (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Atomic Energy Commission Reprints, 5
  - Advisory Committee for Biology and Medicine (ACBM) Radioactive Fallout (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee for Biology and Medicine (ACBM) Reports (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee for Biology and Medicine (ACBM) Reports to Offsite Research Contract Proposals (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Acute Radiation Syndrome (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Argonne, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Argonne, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Brookhaven, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Brookhaven, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Brookhaven, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Brookhaven Monthly Reports, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Brookhaven Monthly Reports, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Brookhaven Monthly Reports, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Health and Safety Laboratory (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Hanford, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Hanford, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Los Alamos, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Medical Board of Review Report, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Oak Ridge, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Oak Ridge, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Oak Ridge, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Press Releases, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - University of California, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Memorabilia, n.d.; 6
  Memorabilia may be closed to scholarly research, subject to the condition of the original items.
- Audiovisual materials, 7
  Biographical / Historical
  Dr. Bugher was a staff member of the Rockefeller Foundation and worked with the U.S. Atomic Energy Commission.
  Scope and Contents
  The RAC has a number of films from the 1920s and 1930s that show Bugher's work on yellow fever in Africa, the Balkans, Greece, and South America. Scenes of villages and traditional practices, malaria treatments, efforts to combat mosquitoes, and some later footage relating to the U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (ca. 1950-1960).
  Alphabetical.
  When requesting to view films -- please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1902).
  If the item does not have a designated AV number, please refer to the Title and the Film Number (which consists of a combination of Roman numerals and alphanumerics - example: III 14.1-6).
  - Africa (Box 1, Dvd AV 836, Reel AV 836)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    All inquires to view films require advanced notice of at least 24 hours, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those not available in modern formats, may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
    Footage from Nigeria and Lagos; rural villages; inspecting school children; the Yellow Fever Research Institute; Asibi
    File Plan
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 15
  - Albania - Sardinia - Terracina, 1931 (Box 1, Dvd AV 838, Reel AV 838)
    Dr. Bishop and Dr. Smillie at work; irrigation plant at Porta Torros; spraying equipment on boat. Produced by Frederick Knipe
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 17
  - Columbia (Box 1, Dvd AV 829, Reel AV 829)
    Footage of rivers, mountains villages, paddle wheel boat pulling logs
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 5
  - Columbia, 1928 (Box 1, Dvd AV 832, Reel AV 832)
    Footage of religious processions, mountains, waterfalls, native fishermen; aerial views of jungle. Produced by H.H. Howard
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 12
  - Columbia (Reel AV 835, Box 1, Dvd AV 835)
    Footage of vaccination program, lab work, rural villages, deforestation
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 14
  - Greece, 1930 (Reel AV 833, Box 1, Dvd AV 833)
    Footage of unsystematic irrigation set-up, a main source of malaria. Villagers washing in contaminated dam; superpictus found in all water sources. Produced by Lewis Hackett.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 13
  - Jungle Yellow Fever (Box 1, Dvd AV 841, Reel AV 841)
    Footage showing sanitary conditions in Buenaventura, Bogota, Columbia, yellow fever research and vaccination efforts. Produced by the Columbian, government with I.H.D. Photography, J.C. Bugher, and Hartley Productions.
    Existence and Location of Copies note
    Two copies of access DVD.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fd 1
  - Malaria in Bulgaria (Reel AV 839, Box 1, Dvd AV 839)
    Footage of scientists inspecting canals, with technical data
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 18
  - O Brasil Naera Atomica (Reel AV 830, Box 1, Dvd AV 830)
    Footage of International Atomic Energy Agency installation (atomic energy exhibit) in Brazil; medical and industrial uses, UN presentation. In Portuguese. Produced by Atualidades Brasileiras Films, producer Herbert Richers.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 6
  - South America (Reel AV 828, Box 1, Dvd AV 828)
    South American jewelry and craft; footage of procession and mule packs
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 4
  - Villavincencio (Reel AV 837, Box 1, Dvd AV 837)
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 16
  - West Africa #1, 1931 (Reel AV 823, Box 1, Dvd AV 823)
    Footage of natives in canoes, village culture, and the Yellow Fever Research Institute (reel 1 of 3). Produced by F. F. Russell.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 1
  - West Africa #2, 1926 (Box 1, Dvd AV 824A, Reel AV 824A)
    Footage of the Yellow Fever Commission work in Lagos: payday for natives, mosquito research, life along the Ogun River (reel 2 of 3). Produced by W.A Sawyer.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 9
  - West Africa #2, 1931 (Box 1, Dvd AV 825, Reel AV 825)
    Footage of natives in canoes, village culture, and the Yellow Fever Research Institute (reel 2 of 2). Produced by F. F. Russell
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 2
  - West Africa #3, 1926 (Box 1, Dvd AV 824B, Reel AV 824B)
    Footage of the Yellow Fever Commission work: scenes in Oshogbo, Clesha, Oyo; women spinning thread, bagging cotton; Baptist Hospital African Mission (reel 3 of 3). Produced by W.A. Sawyer
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 10
  - West African Dancers (Box 1, Dvd AV 831, Reel AV 831)
    Footage of a dance troupe practicing acrobatic routines.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 7
  - West Africa Yellow Fever, 1926 (Box 1, Dvd AV 826, Reel AV 826)
    Footage of the Yellow Fever Commission work in Nigeria and Lagos: fishing, natives at work, parades, dancing, religious rites (reel 1 of 3). Produced by W.A. Sawyer.
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 8
  - Yaba (Box 1, Dvd AV 827, Reel AV 827)
    Footage of village houses, rural roads, women carrying vegetation
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 3
  - Yellow Fever Research Institute (Nigeria) (Box 1, Dvd AV 840, Reel AV 840)
    Footage of main lab and equipment, lab work, taking blood samples, mosquito traps; shots of an eclipse
    IV 2A 2.7 Fb 11
- John C. Bugher photographs, 1056
  Bugher, John C.
  - Bugher (Box 48, Folder 566)
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission (Box 48, Folder 567)
  - Atomic Energy Commission - Awards (Box 48, Folder 568)
  - "Atoms at Work" Exhibit, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Box 49, Folder 569)
  - Cancer Retreat (Box 49, Folder 570)
  - Hiroshima University, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 571)
  - Mexico Trip, c. 1927 (Box 49, Folder 572)
  - Mexico Trip, c. 1927 (Box 49, Folder 573)
  - Mexico Trip, c. 1927 (Box 49, Folder 574)
  - Muzo Yellow Fever Protection Test - Colombia (Box 49, Folder 575)
  - Muzo Yellow Fever Protection Test - Colombia (Box 49, Folder 576)
  - Muzo Yellow Fever Protection Test - Colombia (Box 50, Folder 577)
  - Muzo Yellow Fever Protection Test - Colombia (Box 50, Folder 578)
  - Muzo Yellow Fever Protection Test - Colombia (Box 50, Folder 579)
  - Peking Union Medical College Staff (Box 50, Folder 580)
  - Slides (Box 50, Folder 581)
  - Taylor University, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 582)
  - UNESCO 7th National Conference on Latin America - Subcommittee on Science (Box 50, Folder 583)
  - West African Fisheries Research Institute, Freetown, Sierra Leone (Box 50, Folder 584)
  - West African Fisheries Research Institute, Freetown, Sierra Leone (Box 50, Folder 585)
  - Yellow Fever Research Institute, Yaba, Nigeria (Box 51, Folder 586)
  - Yellow Fever Research Institute, Yaba, Nigeria (Box 51, Folder 587)
  - Yellow Fever Research Institute, Yaba, Nigeria (Box 51, Folder 588)
  - Yellow Fever Research Institute, Yaba, Nigeria (Box 51, Folder 589)
  - Yellow Fever Survey, Mokewa, Ivory Coast (Box 51, Folder 590)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 591)